Anybody home?
有人在家吗?
Hi.
你好.
Hi. Hi Danny.
你好.你好Danny.
How you doing. Lisa?
你好吗,Lisa?
I found that video.
我找到那盘录像带了.
"Mars Needs Women". Excellent.
《火星需要女人》.非常好.
I looked everywhere for it,
我到处找这盘带子,
and I finally went to Video King.
最后在"录像大王"店里找到了.
Michael, it is a great store.
Michael, 那是一家很不错的音像店.
Lisa, how long did you live in California?
Lisa,你在California住了多久?
My whole life until college. Why?
上大学之前一直住那儿.为什么?
I don't know. Maybe I should move to L.A.
我不知道.也许我该搬到洛杉矶去.
What? Why?
什么?为什么?
They have an excellent football team.
那里有一直很好的橄榄球队.
You're pathetic.
你真可怜.
Danny, you don't want to live in California.
Danny,你不会想住在California的.
It's one big disaster area.
那是一个充满灾难的地区.
So? So is my life.
那又怎么样?我的生活也是如此.
No. I mean things like floods.
不.我是指洪水之类的灾难.
And if it isn't a flood, it's a fire or an earthquake. Earthquakes, Danny.
如果不发洪水的话,也会有火灾, 或者地震.地震啊,Danny.
Have you ever been in one?
你经历过地震吗?
Plenty of times.
很多次了.
Most of them are small; you don't feel them.
大多数都是小地震,你感受不到.
But the one in 1990?
但1990年的那一次?
I was going into the airport and the ground started to move.
我正走进机场时, 大地开始震动.
People didn't want to stay in the airport, obviously,
人们不想待在机场里, 当然了,
so they started running out of it, crying and screaming.
所以他们往机场外跑, 哭泣着, 尖叫着.
So?
那又怎么样呢?
The only disasters we have in New England are blizzards.
在新英格兰我们唯一的灾难是暴风雪.
And hurricanes.
还有飓风.
And Danny's love life.
还有Danny的爱情生活.
Danny. Did you and Jeannette break up?
Danny.你和Jeannette分手了吗?
Yep. I dropped her like a hot potato.
是的.我像扔烫手山芋一样把她甩了.
"Typhoon Danny and his Storm of Love",
《台风Danny和他的爱情风暴》.
a new film by Michael Chung.
Michael Chung的新影片.
I like it.
我喜欢这个想法.
Yeah, well, I'm charging you a fortune for the rights.
Yeah, well,那我可要向你收一大笔版权费.